kerneltraining.com 2017-06-09

# Privacy Policy - E-learning Portal with Instructor led Online Training Courses

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which KernelTraining PVT LTD. collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the [www.kerneltraining.com](https://www.kerneltraining.com/) website (“Site”).

#### Personal identification information:

We may collect personal identification information from users in number of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, email address.  
Users may, however, visit our site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain site related activities.

#### Non-personal identification information:

We may collect non-personal identification information of Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about user’s means of connection to our site, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider’s utilized and other similar information.

#### Cookies:

Our site may use “cookies” to enhance user experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. Cookies will never store credit card information as they’re processed using payment gateways that use Secure Encryption Technology.  
How we use collected information? KernelTraining may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

#### To run our website

We may need your information display content on the Site correctly.

#### To personalize user experience

We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.

#### To improve our Site

We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.

#### To send periodic emails

We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.

#### How we protect your information?

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our website.  
Your information will never be sold, exchanged or disclosed to any third party for marketing or any other purposes. You can opt to receive offers from us at any time. You can browse our website without registration.

#### Sharing your personal information:

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners.  
During online training program, we store your contact information in our registration and order entry systems. Your credit card or other important information is never stored in our system as it is processed by our payment gateway which uses Secure Encryption Technology (SSL) system. Our payment processing partners are CCAvenue and PayPal

#### Electronic newsletters:

If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

#### External Links:

Our website may have links to other sites, which include third party websites or resources. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and information practices of third party websites. Please read the privacy policies of third party websites as every website has different terms of use and privacy policies.

#### Course Content:

Course content for all the study programs both online and blended programs, is provided only for the purpose of education and guidance. The course content is reviewed regularly and is subject to change without notice. KernelTraining reserves the right to modify training content without notice.

#### Changes to this privacy policy:

KernelTraining has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site; revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

#### Copyright:

You can copy or take print outs of the website pages, only for your personal use. KernelTraining holds the copyright to all the material on this website. A written permission from the copyright holder must be obtained for any use of this material other than for purposes permitted by law.

#### Image and Video capture policy:

Any images captured during events organized and hosted by KernelTraining should not be misused in any manner. That includes pictures of KernelTraining staff and training participants. If you enroll in a KernelTraining online course your picture may also be featured in photos or videos of the KernelTraining online classes.  
If you do not want us to feature your pictures/testimonials on our web portal or on our social media channels such as Facebook, Twitter, you can send an email to [sales@kerneltraining.com](mailto:sales@kerneltraining.com).

#### Personal Information Corrections:

You can contact us if you notice that the information we are using is incorrect or incomplete in manner. Please send us an email at [sales@kerneltraining.com](mailto:sales@kerneltraining.com)

#### Information deletion:

If you would like to delete your account, please write to [sales@kerneltraining.com](mailto:sales@kerneltraining.com).

#### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this website, you signify your acceptance of this privacy policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our website. Your continued use of the website following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

#### Contact us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at [sales@kerneltraining.com](mailto:sales@kerneltraining.com)
